Hi everyone! I'm in Marrakech for some holidays and we just took some pictures
at the pool and we're going to go to the Medina afterwards to do some photography
as well in the old city. And yeah I just bought this top yesterday at the souk
and I combined it with a small leather harness and some fake leather pants.
And I thought I'm going to show you some more dressing videos since you liked the last ones.
And in this video you will see the first dressing video I ever made
and the other ones are the only latex videos I've done so far.
We'll see you next time.
Thank you.
This light won't let you compromise
The southern reaches of your lonely town
Let's say goodbye to this cellar ghost
Meet me on the water
Face off the swords
Meet me as I die
In the severance inside
guitar solo
Thank you.
So I hope you had fun with these old Instagram dressing videos. I'm going to
enjoy my holiday and I hope you have a nice day. Bye!